[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "Thoughts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Sounds like a good time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "What was -- when you first played here, what was the experience like to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "It was pretty exciting, you know, because, you know, all of us grew up here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "I -- there's a picture somewhere of that, where it's sold out, Friday, Saturday and Sunday, and how much bigger do you get than that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday", "Saturday", "Sunday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Does it not bring back quite the happy memories it does for the others?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Let me see, I remember back when The Byrds played here, The Doors played here, all that stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "And what was it like to realize that dream?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "You know, like it was like a dream come true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "Do you feel lucky?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "I think we're very lucky.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Oh, you're 49?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "I'm 48.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "You're 50?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "No, I'm 60.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "You're 49, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "You look at Mick Jagger and think, he's still bouncing around in his 60s, so can we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", ",", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mick Jagger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "Just grow old disgracefully?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Yes, disgracefully.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Is it all it's cracked up to be, when you look back, do you wish you'd been slightly more temperate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "I think we just had fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "What were you doing, Nikki?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "I was selling light bulbs.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nikki"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "What were you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "I was painting houses.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Mick?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "I was repairing motorcycles.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Amazing, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "-- would you agree with the rest of his assessment?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Aerosmith"], "LOCATION": ["Idaho"]}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Nikki, you've been nerdy, though, haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "IN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "I think -- I grew up in Idaho and I always looked up to these bands like Aerosmith and Kiss and the Stones.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nikki"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "How do you answer to that charge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "That's a pretty good overall description.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Unpredictable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "You know, that, I don't know -- I don't know about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ozzie"]}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Who was the bigger hellraiser?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Well, I think Ozzie did win in the end.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "What were -- what were you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Well, when she would leave, he would ride on our tour bus with us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Ozzie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "CC", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Like, you know, how do you top that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "I can't remember -- I think one or two of you recently described a kind of average day at the height of Motley Crue mania, when you were in the party phase, and it was just utterly compelling, every detail was compelling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "How would it go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "It was just -- it was just one big day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "First thing you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "First thing you do, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Was it a good idea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "EE: We thought it was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "How many times did you do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "Actually, I think it only happened once.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", ":", "DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "No real need to inject it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "There's -- no, that's what we were like.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Did it taste any better coming through your veins?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "It drips down the back of your throat.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Then what happens?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Just at the gig, you know --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Did you ever get rejected?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "The boyfriends would say no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "What sort of drugs are knocking around there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "It's kind of everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Remember the bottle caps?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Well, yes --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "How could I not (INAUDIBLE) what was going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", ":", "NNP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Terrible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Now, the gig ends, you've got a two-hour -- two-hour show, on average?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Yes, two hours.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "What happens back -- is it -- is it sort of heinous backstage, as I always imagined?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Well, it was like the different -- we had the shower rooms.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Clarify?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "You know, we just -- it would just be -- it would just be, you know, girls and drug dealers and just alcohol --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "How many women are backstage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "There was always enough.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "You'd take six?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Yes, he always -- he always took more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "To be the most excessive band ever?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "And that's what the audience was in for the same thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "Do any of you still drink?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "I occasionally drink.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "No drugs anymore?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", ":", ":", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 444, "question": "So you've cleaned up, basically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "Yes, I -- (CROSSTALK)", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Isn't it sad, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "It's a bit sad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Do you feel sad or is it like one of those things that eventually, that's it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "I mean for me, it just quit working and it just started to go the other way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "You nearly died, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "But what was the moment for you when you finally kicked heroin, because it's a notoriously hard drug, you know, to get rid of?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "You know, I went to rehab.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", ":", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", ":", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", ":", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "This arthritis that you have -- how does that affect your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "You know, actually, it's more of an inconvenience than anything else for me, because it's like, you know, standing up straight is -- is real tough for me, because -- just to make a long story short, when I'm on stage, this is the most -- worst part, walking into things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ":", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Walking into microphones, walking into the -- to the drum riser, walking into like sets, things that I want to see on stage that move and do kind of things are like I can't see it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "I sound like a doctor, huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Yes, you do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "-- because it's a chronic condition, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", ":", "CC", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Did that change everything for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "Well, I mean, you know, as a father, you know, you want to be there to protect your children and -- and do whatever you can to keep them safe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "And you knew that, did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "If people want to donate money, how do they do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "SkylarNeil.org.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "As simple as that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "That's it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Tommy, you've got two children, two boys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "CC", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "How old are they now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "Fifteen and almost 14.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "And what's it like for you being a dad with two young teenage sons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "Well, it's -- it's awesome.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "How do you think -- how are you going to deal with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 620, "question": "How do you deal with it, in terms of advice you give to your offspring?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "I've done...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "You've got four kids, right, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "JJ", ",", "DT", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "And have you gotten where you've had to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "I have a 20 -year-old, I have a 17 -year-old, a 16 -year- old and a 10 -year-old.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "Then what do you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "You know, I just try to share with them my experience.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "Want to -- want to -- want to try a number out there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", ":", "JJ", "TO", ":", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "Geez.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Where are we headed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "I'm not -- I'm not touching this one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "I don't think we've ever even really talked about it, have we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "Like Vince said, 50 percent twice is how much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "CD", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Vince"], "PERCENT": ["50 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "Who's the woman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "You know, I'm really happy in a relationship right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 717, "question": "It would be her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 718, "answer": "Yes, it would be her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "The current lady in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 722, "question": "Tommy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 723, "answer": "The same.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "Mick?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "The same.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 762, "question": "Are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 763, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Vegas"]}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 764, "question": "In LA?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 765, "answer": "No, in Vegas.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 766, "question": "In Vegas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 767, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "VB", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "Any regrets?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "I think you just learn by your mistakes, you know, and don't really regret them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", ":", "CC", ":", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 791, "question": "How have you managed to keep this kind of relationship with each other, which seems very good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 792, "answer": "I think we've, you know, we've known each other longer than anybody else besides our parents and -- and -- and brothers and sisters.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 801, "question": "But you'll know that moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 802, "answer": "We're going to know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 809, "question": "What was the -- what was the greatest night of them all, the one -- if you could have a party tonight, you'd have again, what was the one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", ",", "DT", "CD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 810, "answer": "Wow, man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 822, "question": "I could have said any city in the world, couldn't I?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 823, "answer": "I remember that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 831, "question": "Well, I managed -- I got lucky there, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "EX", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 832, "answer": "Got lucky, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 852, "question": "You've never done this before, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 853, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 857, "question": "Well, it's so Vegas, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 858, "answer": "So it's -- it's a perfect fit for us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["February 3rd"]}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 861, "question": "When -- when -- when is it happening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 862, "answer": "It's starting on February 3rd and we're going to be...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", ",", "PRP", ",", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 865, "question": "How do you get tickets?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 866, "answer": "We go to -- we, you, everybody --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 875, "question": "Are you -- are you planning the mother of all shows?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 876, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 879, "question": "Is this going to be the biggest extravaganza?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 880, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WRB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 891, "question": "Another album on the way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 892, "answer": "You know, I think that we're getting to that place where -- I mean, I know I've been writing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 910, "question": "If you could write your own epitaph?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 911, "answer": "Well, I mean I -- I think, you know, with -- with this band, you know, it's just kind of like, you know, we did it our way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 915, "question": "Mick?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 916, "answer": "The palest guy in rock and roll.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 920, "question": "Tommy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 921, "answer": "Oh, God, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 937, "question": "Shall we one more for the road?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CD", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 938, "answer": "Let's go.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]